(LIGHT ROCK MUSIC)
♪ SO LONG AGO I
DON'T REMEMBER WHEN ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN THEY SAID
I LOST MY ONLY FRIEND ♪
♪ WELL THEY SAID SHE DIED EASY
OF A BROKE HEART DISEASE ♪
♪ AS I LISTENED THROUGH
THE CEMETERY TREES ♪
♪ I SEEN THE SUN COMIN' UP
AT THE FUNERAL AT DAWN ♪
♪ WITH THE LONG BROKEN
ARM OF HUMAN LAW ♪
♪ NOW IT ALWAYS
SEEMED SUCH A WASTE ♪
♪ SHE ALWAYS HAD A PRETTY FACE ♪
♪ I WONDERED WHY SHE
HUNG AROUND THIS PLACE ♪
♪♪♪
♪ HEY-EY-EY ♪
♪ COME ON TRY A LITTLE ♪
♪ NOTHING IS FOREVER ♪
♪ GOT TO BE SOMETHING
BETTER THAN IN THE MIDDLE ♪
♪ ME AND CINDERELLA ♪
♪ WE PUT IT ALL TOGETHER ♪
♪ WE CAN DRIVE IT HOME ♪
♪ WITH ONE HEADLIGHT ♪
♪ SHE SAID IT'S COLD ♪
♪ IT FEELS LIKE
INDEPENDENCE DAY ♪
♪ AND I CAN'T BREAK
AWAY FROM THIS PARADE ♪
♪ BUT THERE'S GOT
BE AN OPENING ♪
♪ SOMEWHERE HERE
IN FRONT OF ME ♪
♪ THROUGH THIS MAZE OF
UGLINESS AND GREED ♪
♪ AND I'VE SEEN THE
SIGN UP AHEAD AT THE
COUNTY LINE BRIDGE ♪
♪ SAYIN' ALL IS GOOD AND
NOTHINGNESS IS DEAD ♪
♪ WE RUN UNTIL SHE'S
OUT OF BREATH ♪
♪ SHE RAN UNTIL
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT ♪
♪ SHE HIT THE END,
JUST HER WINDOW LEDGE ♪
♪ HEY-EY-EY ♪
♪ COME ON TRY A LITTLE ♪
♪ NOTHING IS FOREVER ♪
♪ GOT TO BE SOMETHING
BETTER THAN IN THE MIDDLE ♪
♪ BUT ME AND CINDERELLA ♪
♪ WE PUT IT ALL TOGETHER ♪
♪ WE CAN DRIVE IT HOME ♪
♪ WITH ONE HEADLIGHT ♪
♪♪♪
♪ WELL THIS PLACE IS OLD ♪
♪ IT FEELS JUST LIKE
A BEAT UP TRUCK ♪
♪ I TURN THE ENGINE BUT
THE ENGINE DOESN'T TURN ♪
♪ WELL IT SMELLS OF CHEAP
WINE AND CIGARETTES ♪
♪ THIS PLACE IS
ALWAYS SUCH A MESS ♪
♪ SOMETIMES I THINK I'D
LIKE TO WATCH IT BURN ♪
♪ I'M SO ALONE ♪
♪ I FEEL JUST LIKE
SOMEBODY ELSE ♪
♪ MAN, I AIN'T CHANGED, BUT
I KNOW I AIN'T THE SAME ♪
♪ BUT SOMEWHERE HERE ♪
♪ IN BETWEEN THE CITY
WALLS OF DYING DREAMS ♪
♪ I THINK HER DEATH,
IT MUST BE KILLING ME ♪
♪ HEY, HEY, HEY-EY-EY ♪
♪ COME ON TRY A LITTLE ♪
♪ NOTHING IS FOREVER ♪
♪ THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING
BETTER THAN IN THE MIDDLE ♪
♪ ME AND CINDERELLA ♪
♪ WE PUT IT ALL TOGETHER ♪
♪ WE CAN DRIVE IT HOME ♪
♪ WITH ONE HEADLIGHT ♪
♪♪♪